A letter from John Lennon changed his life
Danny Collins is a music, comedy, drama film directed by Dan Fogelman.
An ageing hard-living 1970s rock star decides to change his life when he discovers
a 40-year-old undelivered letter written to him by John Lennon.
Danny Collins, played by Al Pacino.
Mary Sinclair, played by Annette Bening.
Frank Grubman, played by Christopher Plummer.
Samantha Leigh Donnelly, played by Jennifer Garner.
Tom Donnelly, played by Bobby Cannavale.
Guy DeLoach, played by Nick Offerman.
Danny Collins is a 2015 American comedy-drama film written and
directed by Dan Fogelman in his feature directorial debut.
Inspired by the true story of folk singer Steve Tilston, the film stars Al Pacino,
Annette Bening, Jennifer Garner, Bobby Cannavale and Christopher Plummer.
The film was released in theaters on March 20, 2015.
For his performance, Pacino was nominated for the Golden Globe Award for Best Actor
– Motion Picture Musical or Comedy at the 73rd Golden Globe Awards.
The film explores themes of concert, musician, rock star,
based on true story, los angeles, california.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.